# REUBEN GEORGE

#### **CONTACT**



LU2 7DU, Luton, Bedfordshire



07401462942



reuben\_george1998@outlook.com

#### **KEY SKILLS/ACHIEVEMENTS**

- Microsoft Office, including Excel, Word and PowerPoint
- Beginner's level coding knowledge in Iava
- Intermediate level in Python
- Proficient in LaTex
- Base knowledge using Linux OS
- Effective communication skills
- Problem solving
- Research
- Time management
- Excellent organisation skills
- Data analysis
- CyberFirst program alumni

## **HOBBIES & INTERESTS**

Sports – Lacrosse: I played lacrosse for my university team, taking on the role of attack-captain in the 2019/20 season, where I had to organise the team's attack play-by-play alongside providing the captain with additional support with planning training. During the 2020/21 season, I stepped up to become the first team captain. Although COVID made it difficult to organise practice and games, I'd managed to drive a large recruitment campaign for players and keep the level of play steady. Additionally, I was also the first captain in 5 years to lead our team to a varsity win against our rivals.

#### REFERENCES

References are available on request

#### **EDUCATION**

2021

#### **BSc Mathematics**

# University of Southampton, Southampton

- Graduated with Second Class Honours (Upper Division).
- My dissertation was titled "Fundamental stability equations for compact stars" for which I was awarded a first.
- Names of some modules I've studied: "Graph Theory",
  "Mathematical Biology", "Numerical Methods", "Statistical
  Distribution Theory" and "Relativity, Black Holes & Cosmology".

#### **EXPERIENCE**

July 2015 to August 2015

## Research Assistant University of Hertfordshire

- Provided day-to-day professional support to researchers through simple data entry tasks and larger scale data analysis tasks, contributing to overall team efficiency.
- Was awarded the Gold Crest Award for the completion of my project on Analysing High Proper Motion Y-Dwarf Candidates while writing a scientific paper on the subject.

#### October 2017 to May 2018

### Bar Staff Wild Lime

- Effectively communicated with bar staff and customers regarding special requests, and customer's needs.
- Demonstrated time management skills by working upwards of 15 hours a week alongside university studies.
- Great ability to work as part of a team due to the nature of the job itself.
- Provided an enjoyable and friendly customer experience by politely interacting with customers throughout service.

## July 2018 to August 2018

## Summer Intern IBM

- Learned core concepts within cyber security.
- Improved my programming knowledge by working on personal coding projects.
- Working with and learnt about the basics of IBM cloud and using Watson
- Organised an event at the end of the placement for all interns and some staff at IBM.

# July 2020 to August 2020

# Summer Intern Immersive Labs (CyberFirst Virtual Placement)

- Learned core concepts within Cryptography and Threat Intelligence.
- Completed various computer labs associated with the topics above.
- All learning was self-guided, which meant I had to create a rough plan for the 8 weeks and complete the placement accordingly.